<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
  <!-- Define your chatbot's name and personality -->
  <category>
    <pattern>WHAT IS YOUR NAME</pattern>
    <template>My name is FoodBot. I'm your culinary companion, always ready to assist you with your food cravings.</template>
  </category>

  <!-- Handle user queries related to food delivery -->
  <category>
    <pattern>WHAT CAN I ORDER</pattern>
    <template>
      <random>
        <li>You have a world of options at your fingertips! From sushi to burgers, we've got it all.</li>
        <li>Our menu boasts a diverse range of cuisines - Italian, Chinese, Indian, Pakistani, and more!</li>
        <li>Feel free to ask about a specific cuisine, and I'll guide you to the best dishes.</li>
      </random>
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>FIND ME PAKISTANI RESTAURANTS NEARBY</pattern>
 <template>
      Here are some popular Pakistani restaurants in your area:
      <ol>
        <li>Salt Bae - Known for its BBQ dishes like Chicken Tikka and Beef Seekh Kebabs.</li>
        <li>Lahore Grill - A local favorite for Pakistani BBQ cuisine.</li>
        <li>Karachi Kitchen - Offers a variety of Pakistani dishes, including Biryani and Nihari.</li>
        <li>Spice Heaven - Specializes in spicy Pakistani curries and kebabs.</li>
        <li>Tandoori Delights - Famous for its Tandoori Roti and Paneer Tikka.</li>
      </ol>
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>HOW LONG WILL IT TAKE FOR MY ORDER TO ARRIVE</pattern>
    <template>
      <random>
        <li>Delivery times can vary based on the restaurant and your location.</li>
        <li>If you tell me which restaurant you're interested in, I can provide you with an estimated delivery time.</li>
      </random>
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>TELL ME MORE ABOUT Salt Bae</pattern>
    <template><srai>RESTAURANT_INFO</srai></template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>HELP</pattern>
    <template>You can ask me about restaurants, cuisines, or even specific Pakistani dishes. How can I assist you today?</template>
  </category>

  <!-- Handle user preferences and recommendations -->
  <category>
    <pattern>I'M IN THE MOOD FOR PAKISTANI BBQ</pattern>
    <template>
      <random>
        <li>Great choice! Let's explore Pakistani BBQ cuisine together. How about trying Seekh Kebabs from <set>recommended_restaurant=<srai>RECOMMEND_RESTAURANT</srai></set>? It's a crowd favorite!</li>
        <li>Pakistani BBQ cuisine is delightful! I recommend Chicken Boti from <get>cuisine</get>. Would you like to know more about it?</li>
      </random>
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>RECOMMEND A POPULAR PAKISTANI BBQ DISH</pattern>
    <template>
      <random>
        <li>One of the most popular dishes in Pakistani BBQ cuisine is Chicken Tikka. It's a culinary masterpiece!</li>
        <li>For an unforgettable Pakistani BBQ experience, you must try Beef Seekh Kebabs from <set>recommended_restaurant=<srai>RECOMMEND_RESTAURANT</srai></set>.</li>
      </random>
    </template>
  </category>

  <!-- Handle generic greetings -->
  <category>
    <pattern>HELLO</pattern>
    <template>
      <random>
        <li>Hello there! Ready to embark on a culinary adventure?</li>
        <li>Hi! Let's explore the world of Pakistani flavors together!</li>
      </random>
    </template>
  </category>

  <category>
    <pattern>HI</pattern>
    <template>
      <random>
        <li>Hi! Hungry for some good Pakistani food? You're in the right place!</li>
        <li>Hi there! I'm your Pakistani food guide. What can I assist you with today?</li>
      </random>
    </template>
  </category>

  <!-- Handle fallback responses -->
  <category>
    <pattern>*</pattern>
    <template>
      <random>
        <li>I apologize, but I didn't quite catch that. Please rephrase your question or ask me something related to Pakistani food delivery.</li>
        <li>Oops! It seems I missed that. Please try asking a food-related question, and I'll do my best to help.</li>
      </random>
    </template>
  </category>

  <!-- Define wildcard patterns for cuisines -->
  <category>
    <pattern>LIST_CUISINES</pattern>
    <template>Italian, Chinese, Indian, Mexican, Thai, Pakistani BBQ, and more!</template>
  </category>

  <!-- Define a category for providing Pakistani restaurant information -->
  <category>
    <pattern>RESTAURANT_INFO</pattern>
    <template>Let me give you some information about Salt Bae. Salt Bae is a renowned Pakistani restaurant known for its exquisite BBQ dishes, including Chicken Tikka and Beef Seekh Kebabs. Customers often praise the restaurant's flavorful cuisine and efficient service. The average delivery time from Salt Bae is approximately 30 minutes to 45 minutes, depending on your location.</template>
  </category>

  <!-- Define a category for recommending a Pakistani restaurant based on cuisine -->
  <category>
    <pattern>RECOMMEND_RESTAURANT</pattern>
    <template>
      <random>
        <li>How about trying Pakistani BBQ cuisine from Salt Bae? They offer an exceptional dining experience!</li>
        <li>You might enjoy Pakistani BBQ cuisine at Lahore Grill. It's a local favorite!</li>
      </random>
    </template>
  </category>

  <!-- Define a topic for managing user preferences -->
  <topic name="USER_PREFERENCES">
    <category>
      <pattern>MY FAVORITE CUISINE IS PAKISTANI BBQ</pattern>
      <template>Great choice! I'll remember that Pakistani BBQ is your favorite cuisine.</template>
      <think><set>cuisine=Pakistani BBQ</set></think>
    </category>
  </topic>
</aiml>
